A-ori.
I already decided that the first
person I'd look at if I ever gained sight
would be myself.
The person I hate the most.
Unable to do anything alone,
and everything a struggle.
Always troubling people around me.
I'd fall all the time and hurt myself.
The person I hate the
most in the world: me.
So this is... me.
I'm not dashing.
No beard, either.
Well, that's because I'm a child.
I had wondered if looking at my face
would make me hate myself even more,
or if perhaps it'd make me happy.
But I am still me, after all.
It's rather anticlimactic.
Hey, do you think I can
come to like myself?
And... what are you?
KUNON THE SORCERER CAN SEE
I doubt it, but...
Is it you, Iko—
Did you call for me?
It's immaterial?
Master Kunon?
Iko?
Yes?
Iko.
Yes... Master Kunon!
Is your hair in a braid?
Yes, it is!
I didn't know maid outfits
symbolized cleanliness so well.
A gentleman would first tell me that
it looks good on me and I look cute!
So you did it! You made it happen!
Yes, I can see now.
Congratulations!
I'm so happy for you, Master Kunon!
I feel dizzy! You'll make me sick!
Oh, sorry!
We should let your father know right away!
I must cook up a feast for tonight!
Listen, aren't you in the mood
for some creamy crab croquettes?
Is that your request? I can do that!
Iko, do you... have a horn on your head?
No. I do when I get mad, but right
now I'm happy so it's pulled in!
Is that so?
Now I can see your charming
face and your sexy horn.
I'm glad I didn't say that.
So this is... scenery.
That's not what I expected!
Master Kunon, it's still chilly outside.
Thank you.
Let us go.
I'm sure everyone will be over the moon.
You're right.
By the way, do you see
something behind me?
Oh my! Is this a scary story? I love it!
Let me hear it!
No, never mind.
What?! I'd love to hear it!
The experiment was a massive success.
Now I can see, but...
I can see, but...!
You can see now?!
Yes.
You did it!
Kunon.
I'm so glad! So glad!
I'm proud of you, Kunon.
Mother.
Kunon?
Well, um...
Why do they look super cool?!
It's just that you look so cool.
Mother looks beautiful, you mean?
Uh, yeah! Like a heroine
from an epic adventure?
Are you saying I'm a
heroine, like a princess?
Oh, Kunon.
No, the one holding the sword.
Do I look cool, too?
Yes, very much.
Do your parents happen to be
fallen angels by any chance?
They are your parents, too,
so you know the answer.
Yes, I do know that, but...
Say, Iko, are there humans
with wings in this world?
Every single one of us is born with wings.
By spreading the wings called
freedom and potential,
we can soar into the sky of the mind.
But as we get older,
we forget how to do it.
The crab, the horn,
the eyes of a heroine from an adventure
and the wings of a fallen angel.
Until a few years ago... I mean,
I'm still young and fresh!
They are immaterial,
and only I can see them.
Why is that?
Kunon! Kunon!
Oh, Father has returned.
Both Mother and Brother are the badass
type, so Father must also be...
Finally... Finally, you did it.
I don't even understand what he is!
Darling! That's right.
Kunon finally did it!
Well done! Good job!
Tonight, we celebrate!
We must send word to the castle, too.
Let's decorate with a lot of beautiful
flowers Kunon can enjoy looking at.
I'm going to cook tons of creamy
crab croquettes, so you just wait!
Brother.
Hm?
Is a father usually like
fog within a family?
Don't ever say that out loud!
You'll make Father cry for real!
Okay.
I'll ask my master for advice.
Excuse me.
Who said you could enter?
Oh, wow. This is my first time seeing
the floor of Mr. Zeon's room.
We can't thank Kunon enough, can we?
Eek!
State your business. Otherwise, begone.
Grand Master's message.
His Majesty has granted you permission
to go outside, so you can go.
What?
Apparently there's good news.
Is it Kunon?
Oh, he's here.
Oh, right.
Kunon!
Your Highness, it's been a while.
Sister Raysha told me!
You finally made your dream come true!
Yes.
Is this it?
Yes. It's the eye of mirrors
that reflects everything.
I'm calling it the Glass Eye.
Will you take a look at my face?
Yes, it'd be my pleasure!
I've worked hard so I can
see Your Highness's face!
I'm just so excited, my heart
is bouncing like a young boy!
I am a young boy, in fact.
Gorgeous blonde like the
rays of the morning sun.
Ice blue eyes.
You're just as beautiful as
I imagined, if not more...
Of course!
Kunon?
Am I not your type?
That will never be true when
it comes to you, Your Highness!
You're more than I imagined!
Really?
Yes, you're just like a
feather of a beautiful bird!
A feather?
He means the wings of
freedom and potential.
If the young and fresh Princess
Mirika is flying freely in the sky,
a large, middle-aged man with a beard
will come catch you in a silver cage!
As always, your analogy is scary.
Right now, Your Highness has
the skill to take down a
large, middle-aged man
with a beard in one hit.
Congratulations on your achievement.
Thank you very much.
Um... that's a very cool sword.
This? It's my partner.
Sure, that one.
Sir Dario is also the badass type.
Yo, Kunon.
Now you're summoning me. Look at
you moving up the ladder, huh?
And who the heck do we have here?!
Uh... Are you my master?
I can't see you well
because you're too bright.
Too bright? Of course I am.
I am always shining.
What are you talking about?
N-No, that's not quite what I mean...
Sir Dario has a white great sword.
Master's whole body is shining brightly.
Maybe a similar type to Father?
I am seeing something.
Master. Agh! No, I can't!
Master, there's something
I'd like to discuss alone.
This is no laughing matter.
But it doesn't make sense at all!
You have a giant crab with you?
And Dario has a ginormous blade?
And Her Highness has a quill
sticking out of her head?!
From now on, when I ask for
Her Highness's hand in marriage,
or move into a new residence,
I'll be carrying a crab and
Her Highness will have a quill
sticking out of her head!
Your future plan is pretty solid, huh?
The colors of the scenery
you see also seem different, huh?
And you say I'm shining.
Well, I've got to admit
I'm always shining.
Among humans, I'm the
brightest in the world.
Obviously not as bright as the sun.
Nope, I can't do it.
Look at me.
I really can't.
You're so bright I can't
look at you directly!
I have two guesses, primarily speaking.
Okay.
One is the possibility where you're
seeing the shapes of souls.
You mean something spiritual?
But then, that would
mean my soul is a crab.
The other is the pattern where magic
sickness is causing visual hallucination.
Sickness from magic?
Some locations can
accumulate magical power,
while other places can be
pathways of magical power.
I've been to one of those spots.
It rendered me useless,
like I got drunk after too many drinks.
In the fading consciousness,
I saw things that were immaterial.
Things that were immaterial.
Sounds similar, right?
Yes.
But we can't determine which this is.
Not enough data.
If you see more, we might find a pattern.
Um, Master?
Hm?
Could this have been a failure?
That's not possible.
Because it's the masterpiece
of my beloved student.
There are many
creatures in nature that do not see
colors, creatures with many eyes,
and creatures that can't see, like you.
No one knows what's the right way to see.
You can have your own
way of seeing things.
Yes, sir!
And who knows? Maybe what you see might
be telling you something very important.
If it's really tough for you,
you can seal it.
But if not, keep on seeing.
You're right.
I've only started to see, after all.
For now, don't tell anyone
that you're seeing things
until you figure out the
pattern and the conclusion.
There may be people who find it strange.
Yes. I'm glad I asked for advice!
You're still blinding!
My radiance is amazing!
They're still talking?
His eyeballs were just completed.
I'm sure he has much to discuss.
I'm sure he does.
Kunon's birthday is coming up soon, right?
Yes.
What gift would make Kunon happy?
I'm sure he'll be happy with
anything from you, Princess Mirika.
Y-You think so?
Your Highness!
I'm sorry to have kept you waiting.
Kunon!
Master!
Come on, just imagining
a quill sticking out...
Is everything okay?
Oh, nothing. Just a private
conversation with Master.
What were you talking to
Iko about, Your Highness?
A private conversation.
Right, Your Highness?
Yes.
What would you like to
do with these books?
I read them all, so I'll leave them
at the library of the main building.
I never knew this room was so spacious.
You're right.
Kunon, happy 12th birthday.
Happy birthday, Kunon!
Happy birthday!
Thank you, Your Highness.
Father, Mother, Brother, thank you.
It might be a bit heavy,
but it's sturdy and will last long.
Thank you, Father.
Here you go, Kunon.
Study a lot with this.
I will. Thank you very much.
Here's my gift!
A map for foodies?
Yeah, I looked up good restaurants
on the way to the magic school.
Gotta have something to look
forward to on your trip, right?
The school's pretty far away, so...
It's very... far away, isn't it?
Kunon, you're moving so far away.
D-Don't you worry, Mother!
He'll graduate in no time!
That's right.
Even if he's far away,
he'll still love you.
Right, Kunon?
Yes, of course.
Come on, we're celebrating today.
Let's enjoy ourselves.
Okay.
Now, let us eat!
Yes, I'll start serving right away!
Are you finished preparing for your trip?
Yes. I'm taking comfortable
clothes and bare necessities.
Anything else I need, I will buy there.
I have school on the day you depart,
so I'm sorry I can't see you off.
Please don't worry about it.
You have something you
must do, Your Highness.
Yes.
Kunon, happy birthday.
Thank you very much. May I open it?
Of course.
A bracelet!
Thank you!
It's a matching pair.
Wow...
Matching with Your Highness,
it outshines any royal crown.
Even my master will have
wisdom tooth pain from the stress
if I shower him with this radiance!
If and when things get
tough at the magic school,
please speak to it like it's me.
I will do the same.
Your Highness.
I will write to you.
As will I.
I will come back to you, no matter what.
I will be waiting.
Please be well until then.
Same to you, Kunon.
Kunon.
Let's see him off without tears.
I'm sure he's feeling
more anxious than anyone.
Yes, you're right.
Okay, bye for now.
So unconcerned!
Doesn't he have more to say?
No, that was very Kunon.
Okay, bye for now!
So it came from you!
Kunon changed a lot because of that maid.
Changed in a good way, I think.
In a good way, I hope.
A-ori.
See you! In two, three,
four, or five years?
Anyhow, I'll come home in a few years!
Right. Take care.
Don't catch a cold, Kunon!
I won't! Goodbye!
Magic school. I wonder what kinds
of sorcerers I'll meet there.
Wait up, wait up!
Let me hop on, too!
Saint Reyes.
It is time to depart for the magic school.
Very well.
NEXT EPISODE: FAREWELLS
AND HELLOS AND DIRASHIK
Next episode: "Farewells
and Hellos and Dirashik."